secretbuilders.com 2018-12-27

# SecretBuilders

SecretBuilders Privacy Policy Back to Home

SecretBuilders is a online, virtual world where children can explore, create and interact with each other. Their safety and privacy are of utmost importance to us and our practices are designed to be in compliance with the United States Federal Trade Commission's Children's Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA), effective April 21, 2000. Parents are strongly encouraged to participate in their children's online activities and monitor use of e-mails and engagement in other electronic communication. For more information about COPPA or children's privacy, please visit <http://www.ftc.gov/privacy/privacyinitiatives/childrens.html> and <http://www.coppa.org/>.

The SecretBuilders Safety Rules also provide more information about how to be safe online. Players must agree to follow these rules before playing on SecretBuilders.

The purpose of our privacy policy is to inform you about the types of information we gather about you online when you visit our site, how we may use that information, and whether we disclose it to anyone.

We do NOT require any personally identifiable information that can be used to individually identify a user offline. For example, first name and age are personal information but they do not specifically identify you in the way full name (first and last name), e-mail address and postal address can. Never give that kind of information to anybody online. When registering with SecretBuilders we ask that you NOT use your real name as your username.

Players are required to provide a valid email address upon registration only for account maintenance purposes, such as resending lost or forgotten password. We also require registration by age group in order to comply with federal guidelines for protecting children younger than 13 years of age. If a child selects a age group indicating that he/she is under 13, we require a parent's email address through which we notify the parent that his/her child has registered at our site as required under COPPA.

If you contact us by e-mail, we use your e-mail address (which is personally identifiable information) only to respond to your specific request or question.

In the future we may collect information such as gender and age to provide us with valuable demographics in order to continue developing and improving our site. Any such information will only be used internally to improve our site and will not be used to identify a single user.

We may also collect information vis-a-vis surveys, Build It!, questionnaires and other online feedback. Any information collected thus will be aggregated and will not contain any personally identifiable information.

SecretBuilders employs various communication tools to facilitate interactivity and richness within our online world and to enhance our safety features by eliminating, to the extent possible, reliance on emails as a mode of communication. These in-world tools include: chat; mail from SecretBuilders Council and Admin in response to magazine postings, contest entries and other activities; buddy list mail and messaging; and bulletin boards. SecretBuilders will primarily use these modes to communicate with users regarding new features, announcements, etc. rather than email.

SecretBuilders chat, internal mail and messaging, and bulletin boards are protected by a sophisticated advanced filter technology, and selectively monitored by staff moderators as well as peer reporters. These communications tools however are NOT moderated continuously on a 24-hour basis and some messages may get through the filters and may be offensive to some players. The Panic Button will allow players to report violation of rules by other players. Please read the SecretBuilders Safety Rules to ensure as much online safety as possible.

We, or someone authorized on our behalf, will routinely collect our users' IP addresses and browser information to track visit information and traffic patterns such as places and sites visited on SecretBuilders, the date and time of the visit, areas of interest or appeal, etc. We also send cookies, small bits of information to a user's computer, to allow us to remember each user as he/she travels around SecretBuilders.� We recommend that you enable the option "cookies that are sent back to their originating servers" on your browser. Our cookies do NOT remain on your machine after you leave SecretBuilders.

We use this information for improving content and services and for investigating cases of suspected abuse. None of the information collected is personally identifiable information about you.

Personally identifiable information will not be provided in any form to third parties except in cases where such information is required by a service provider for our use for direct communications with you, but such information will be restricted in all cases exclusively to our access and use.

We may disclose personally identifiable information to third parties as required by law enforcement or other governmental agencies, to comply with court orders, to enforce our Terms and Conditions, or to protect the rights, property, safety of our website and other users of the site.

We may engage third parties to assist with services related to the website, such as technical and processing services, contest fulfillment, mailings, and analyzing website performance. These third parties are obligated to keep the information secure and confidential and must use the information only in connection with providing services to SecretBuilders and Renaissance Media2.0.

We may share **aggregated** statistical data with our sponsors, partners, or the general public for partnership, research or marketing purposes but will never give out data on individual users that can be personally identifiable. In the event that any further information or participation from a user under 13 is needed, permission from a parent or guardian will be required.

In the event that any or all of the assets related to the SecretBuilders or Renaissance Media 2.0 are transferred or sold to another entity, all information, including personally identifiable information would to be transferred to that entity.

SecretBuilders is owned and operated by Renaissance 2.0 media. You can contact us at:[ admin@ren20.com](mailto:admin@ren20.com)

THIS PRIVACY POLICY WAS LAST UPDATED ON March 18, 2008

The online experiences and activities described in this web site may be available now or planned for future, and this version reflects our current policies on information collection, use and disclosure. We reserve the right to change this policy at any time, and will post any changes to this policy as soon as they go into effect on this site.

trademarks owned by Renaissance 2.0 Media Inc.  
2005-2007 - ALL RIGHTS RESERVED  
PATENT PENDING
